Finding aid for the Henry Clay Frick Papers, Series II: Correspondence, 1882-1929, undated HCFF.1.2
The Frick Collection/Frick Art Reference Library Archives
- Bryan - Buffington, E.J. (Box 10, Folder 8)
  Bryant, John Cullen, 1905
  Bryant, L.M., Mrs., 1915
  Bryant, P.F., 1915
  Bryson, D.M., 1914
  Buchanan, Walter J., 1910
  Buchanan, Eliza M (Mrs. James I. Buchanan), 1903-1910
  Buck, John H., 1920
  Buckham, Robert B., 1905
  Buckman, Marie N., 1911
  Bucknell College (Lewisburg, Pa.), 1903
  Buckner, M.L.S., 1900
  Buckner, Thos. A., 1913
  Budd, Samuel, 1898, 1915
  Buffington, E.J., 1903-1906
- Buffington, Joseph, 1901-1919 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Buildings - Bureau (Box 10, Folder 10)
  Buildings and Building Management(Chicago, Ill.), 1921
  Bullard, A.H., Mrs., 1916
  Bullard, H.W., 1886
  Bullard, R.E., 1908
  Bullinger, Edward W., 1916
  Bullitt, John C., 1886
  Bullitt, Logan M., 1896-1898
  Bullitt, William C., 1897, 1905
  Bumstead, Horace, Mrs., 1914
  Buntin, William C., 1916
  Burden, I. Townsend, Mrs., 1918
  Bureau of Corporation Statistics (New York, N.Y.), 1905
  Bureau of Municipal Research (New York, N.Y.), 1907
- Burgess - Burnham (Box 11, Folder 1)
  Burgess, Kathryn A. (Mrs. E.C. Burgess), 1911
  Burgesses Corps [Albany, N.Y.], 1909
  Burghardt, Louis, 1912
  Burgher, F.I., 1918
  Burgwin, A.P., 1898
  Burgwin, Mildred Carlisle (Mrs. A.P. Burgwin), 1907, 1909
  Burgwin, George C., 1915, 1917
  Burk, A.W., 1903
  Burke, Henry W., 1890
  Burke, James Francis, 1919
  Burleigh, A.R., 1918
  Burlington Magazine Limited(London, England), 1907
  Burnham, Austin A., 1898
  Burnham, D.H., 1897-1912
  Burnham, Daniel H., [Jr.], 1918
  Burnham, Williams and Co. (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1897
- Burns - Butler, J.G., Jr. (Box 11, Folder 2)
  Burns and Giltinan (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1902, 1904
  Burns Detective Agency (New York, N.Y.), 1912, 1915
  Burns, Francis X., 1892-1903
  Burns, R.G., 1898
  Burns, Winnie, 1906
  Burr, Edwin H., 1918
  Burr, Jacob, 1910
  Burrelle's Press Clipping Bureau (New York, N.Y.), 1919
  Burroughs, Bryson, 1911, 1914
  Burt, J.H., 1902
  Burt, R.N., 1919
  Burton Brothers and Co. (New York, N.Y.), 1901
  Burton, Robert, 1917
  Burwell, E.L., 1910
  Bush, J. Adriance, 1891
  Bush, S.D., 1909-1911
  Bussell, Walter, 1902-1905
  Butcher, Sydney E., 1914
  Butler, E.H., 1905
  Butler, George P., 1921
  Butler, H.A., 1910
  Butler, J.G., Jr., 1903-1921
- Butler, Nicholas - Byrne (Box 11, Folder 3)
  Butler, Nicholas M., 1907-1916
  Butler, S.M., 1905
  Bulter, Howard Russell, 1898
  Butler-Ward Co. (New York, N.Y.), 1903
  Butterman, S., 1886
  Byers, A.M., undated
  Byers, John W., 1902-1903
  Byington, Edwin H., 1903-1909
  Byrne and Wise (Scottdale, Pa.), 1886
  Byrne, John R., 1891
  Byrne, P.J., 1902, 1909
- C. and G. Cooper - C.R. Williams (Box 11, Folder 4)
  C. and G. Cooper Co. (Mt. Vernon, Ohio), 1909
  C.C. Mellor Co., Ltd. (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1903-1904
  C.C. Mengel and Bro. Co. (Louisville, Ky.), 1909
  C.F. Anderson and Company (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1906
  C.J. Spellman and Sons [no place], 1902
  C. Keur and Sons [?, France], 1903
  C.R. Williams and Co. (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1901
- Cabot - Cain (Box 11, Folder 5)
  Cabot, Charles M., 1915
  Cabot, George E., 1916
  Cabot, Susan B., 1905
  Cadman, A.W., 1885, 1897-1898
  Cadwalader, John L., 1911
  Cadwell, Karl H., 1920
  Cahall Water Tube Boilers (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1901
  Cain, Wm. H., 1894
- Calder - Calvary (Box 11, Folder 6)
  Calder, Sadie S. Pierce [Mrs. H.W. Calder], 1915, 1919
  Caldwell, John, 1893, 1898
  Caldwell, L.M., 1898
  Caldwell, Robert B., 1898-1917
  Call, Z.G., 1899
  Callaway, S.R., 1899
  Callendar, A., 1919, 1921
  Calumet Coke Co. (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1889-1894
  Calvary P.E. Church [Pittsburgh, Pa.], 1905-1907
- Cambon - Cambria (Box 11, Folder 7)
  Cambon, Jules, 1902
  Cambria Iron Co. (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1886-1894
  Cambria Steel Co. (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1906-1915
- Cameron - Campion (Box 11, Folder 8)
  Cameron, J.D., 1896-1908
  Cameron, J.M., 1900-1901
  Cameron, L., 1921-1922
  Campbell, A.B., 1908
  Campbell and Co. (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1890
  Campbell, Clidor, 1919
  Campbell, Edward, 1907
  Campbell, Geo. J., 1907
  Campbell, J.A., 1903
  Campbell, John, [1901?]
  Campbell, John H., 1890
  Campbell, Nigel L., 1905
  Campbell, O.M., 1910
  Campbell, W[?]J., 1888
  Campion, Ansel G., 1906-1910
- Candee - Cannon (Box 11, Folder 9)
  Candee, Helen, 1913
  Canenin, Regis, 1901-1903
  Canfield, R.D., 1910
  Canfield, R.R., 1893
  Canfield, Richard, undated
  Canfield, Sue H., 1905-1910
  Cann and Taylor (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1899
  Cannon, Jas. G., 1893-1896
  Cannon, J[oseph] G[urney], 1906
- Caparn - Caprillian (Box 11, Folder 10)
  Caparn, H.A., 1910
  Cape Ann Golf Club (Rockport, [Mass.]) - See: George F. Babbitt
  Cappeau, Lemley and Miller Company (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1911
  Capital City Club (Atlanta, Ga.), 1895
  Capps, W.L., 1893
  Caprillian, Elisha, 1917, 1918
- Carbondale - Carmer (Box 11, Folder 11)
  Carbondale Machine Co. (Carbondale, Pa.), 1903
  Carborundum Co. (Niagara Falls, N.Y.), 1913, 1919
  Carew, Lucie[?] B., 1907
  Cargo, Warren S., 1900
  Carhart, W.N., 1898
  Carlis, W.W., 1909
  Carlisle, James D., 1898
  Carlisle, Lillian, 1909
  Carmer, Herbert N., 1916
- Carnegie, Andrew, 1882-1898, 1912, undated (Box 12, Folder 1-4)
- Carnegie, Andrew, II [son of Thomas M. Carnegie], 1910 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Carnegie Brothers - Carnegie, Thomas (Box 13, Folder 1)
  Carnegie Brothers and Co., Limited (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1887-1891
  Carnegie Institute (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1910
  Carnegie Library (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1915
  Carnegie, Lucy C., 1892-1900
  Carnegie, Margaret Thaw [Mrs. Thomas M. Carnegie], 1906, 1914
  Carnegie Museum [Pittsburgh, Pa.], 1912
  Carnegie, Phipps and Co., Limited (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1888
  Carnegie Steel Co., Limited (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1892-1919
  Carnegie, Thomas M., [1843-1886], [188]5, undated
  Carnegie, Thomas M., 1906
- Carothers - Carr, Myrtie (Box 13, Folder 2)
  Carothers, James, 1897
  Carpenter, E.P., 1886
  Carpenter, Fannie, 1888
  Carpenter, Geo. M., 1899
  Carpenter, H.M., 1903
  Carpenter, J. McF., 1910
  Carpenter, Jno. Q., 1900
  Carpenter, Sanford N., 1905
  Carr, C.H., 1916
  Carr, Hinton E., 1905
  Carr, Myrtie W., 1913
- Carr, William A., 1895-1914 (Box 13, Folder 3-7)
- Carr, Wm. Wilkins - Carstairs, C. Haseltine (Box 13, Folder 8)
  Carr, Wm. Wilkins, 1899
  Carrère and Hastings (New York, N.Y.), 1912-1916
  Carrick, William C., 1901
  Carrington, W.T., 1916
  Carroll, Charles A., Mrs., 1901
  Carroll, L.A., 1915
  Carson, Jessie M., 1915
  Carson, John L., 1894
  Carstairs, Betty, 1914
  Carstairs, C. Haseltine, 1913-1914
- Carstairs, Charles S., 1897-1919 (Box 13, Folder 9-11)
- Carstairs, D.H. - Cary (Box 13, Folder 12)
  Carstairs, D.H., 1918
  Carstairs, Daniel, Mrs., 1917
  Carstaris, J.H., 1904
  Carstairs, James, 1915
  Carter Electric Company (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1902, 1904
  Carter, Frank F., 1919
  Carter, G.[V?]., 1900
  Carter, Isabel May (Mrs. Thomas W. Carter), 1917
  Carter, Mrs. J.T., 1901
  Carter, Jesse Benedict, 1912
  Carter, Mary A.E., 1902
  Cartier, Pierre / Cartier (New York, N.Y.), 1918-1919
  Cary Smith and Barbey (New York, N.Y.), 1901
- Cascapedia - Cass (Box 13, Folder 13)
  Cascapedia Club [Quebec, Canada], 1908-1919
  Case, Albert C., 1899, 1901
  Cass, Eleanore Baldwin, 1916
- Cassatt, Alexander J., 1899-1906 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Casselberry - Castalia (Box 14, Folder 2)
  Casselberry, Horace, 1903
  Cassell and Company, Limited (New York, N.Y.), 1889
  Cassell, W.A., 1908
  Cassier's Magazine(New York, N.Y.), 1899
  Casson, Herbert N., 1906
  Castalia Sporting Club (Cleveland, Ohio), 1897-1915
- Caster - Central National (Box 14, Folder 3)
  Caster, A., 1893
  Castner, Curran and Bullitt (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1904
  Caswell, Edwin Whittier, 1909
  Catholic Total Abstinence Society [no place], 1912
  Catholic Women's League (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1916
  Caton, Adda O., 1901
  Caton and Co. (Irwin, Pa.) / W.J. Caton, 1894
  Cauldwell-Wingate Co. (New York, N.Y.), 1915
  Caullet, J.[?], 1919
  Cawley, George, 1894
  Census Bureau [no place], 1910
  Central District and Printing Telegraph Co. (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1898-1912
  Central National Bank (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1890-1900
- Central New - Cerro (Box 14, Folder 4)
  Central New England Railway Co. (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1900, 1903
  Central News and Press Exchange (New York, N.Y.), 1907
  Central Railroad Co. of New Jersey (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1904
  Central Young Women's Christian Association (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1899-1900
  Century Theatre (New York, N.Y.), 1916
  Cerro de Pasco Investment Co. (New York, N.Y), 1903-1925
- Chadwick - Chambrun (Box 14, Folder 5)
  Chadwick, Cornelia J., 1917
  Chalfant, John W., 1888-1906
  Chalfant, John W., Jr., 1906
  Chamber of Commerce of Pittsburgh (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1906-1919
  Chamber of Commerce of the State of New York (New York, N.Y.), 1907-1910
  Chamberlain, John, 1887
  Chambers, J.F., 1907
  Chambers, Joseph H., 1895
  Chambers, Julius, [1906], 1911
  Chambers, M.S., 1916
  Chambrun, Clara Longworth, 1917
- Champeno - Charles Scribner's Sons (Box 14, Folder 6)
  Champeno, Mary, 1894
  Chandler Bros. Co. [no place], 1909
  Chandler, J.H., 1897
  Chantler, Thomas D., 1910
  Chapin, Harriet E., 1915
  Chapman, Alva P., 1890
  Chapman, Henry T., 1898
  Chapman, John A., 1906
  Chapman, W.O. - See: Asiatic National Bank
  Chappuis and Rapier (New Orleans, La.), 1900
  Chapple, Joe Mitchell, 1917
  Chappotin, J.B., Mrs., 1913
  Charity Organization Society (New York, N.Y.), 1909
  Charles Graef and Co. (New York, N.Y.), 1899, 1902
  Charles H. Fuller Co. (Toledo, Ohio), 1913
  Charles Hathaway and Co. (New York, N.Y.), 1894-1896
  Charles, Heinrich, 1908
  Charles Scribner's Sons (New York, N.Y.), 1915-1917
- Charles Smith and Sons (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1885-1890 (Box 14, Folder 7-9)
- Charles Smith and Sons (continued), 1891-1901 (Box 15, Folder 1-4)
- Charleston, Parkersburg and Western Railway Co. (Charleston, W.Va.), 1916 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Charley, C.L., 1901-1906 (Box 15, Folder 6-8)
- Charlotte - Chartran (Box 15, Folder 9)
  Charlotte Furnace Co., Ltd. (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1890
  Charlton, Loudon, 1911
  Chartiers Railway Co. (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1886-1897, undated
  Chartran, E. [Mrs. Theobald Chartran?], 1901
  Chartran, [Theobald], 1899
- Chas. D. Barney and Co. (Philadelphia, Pa., and New York, N.Y.), 1901 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Chas. D. Barney and Co. (continued), 1902-1904 (Box 16, Folder 1-8)
- Chas. D. Barney and Co. (continued), 1905-1906 (Box 17, Folder 1-6)
- Chas. D. Barney and Co. (continued), 1907-1910 (Box 18, Folder 1-6)
- Chas. D. Barney and Co. (continued), 1910-1911 (Box 19, Folder 1-6)
- Chas. D. Barney and Co. (continued), 1911-1918 (Box 20, Folder 1-6)
- Chas. D. Barney and Co. (continued), 1919-1924 (Box 21, Folder 1-5)
- Chase - Chicago and Minnesota (Box 21, Folder 6)
  Chase, Christopher H., 1906
  Chase, Edward L., 1898, 1902
  Chase, J. Eastman, 1899-1900, 1915
  Chase National Bank [no place], 1914
  Châtelain, R.A., 1897
  Chesebrough, A.S., 1900
  Cheney, B.P., 1913
  Cheyne, James A., 1911
  Chicago and Eastern Illinois Railroad Co. (Chicago, Ill.), 1901
  Chicago and Minnesota Ore Co. (Chicago, Ill.), 1890, undated
- Chicago and Northwestern Railway Co. (Chicago, Ill.), 1906-1919 (Box 21, Folder 7-8)
- Chicago City -Chicago Examiner (Box 22, Folder 1)
  Chicago City and Connecting Railways Collateral Trust (Chicago, Ill.), 1915-1923
  Chicago Club (Chicago, Ill.), 1886-1917
  Chicago Examiner(Chicago, Ill.), 1914
- Chicago Furnace - Childs, Harvey (Box 22, Folder 2)
  Chicago Furnace Co. (Chicago, Ill.), 1892
  Chicago, Lake Shore and Eastern Railway Co. (Chicago, Ill.), 1904
  Chicago Ornamental Iron Co. (Chicago, Ill.), 1902
  Chicago Rock Island and Pacific Railway Co. (New York, N.Y.), 1903
  Chicago, St. Paul, Minneapolis and Omaha Railway Co. [no place], 1919
  Chicago Tribune(Chicago, Ill.), 1903
  Chidester, H., 1911
  Child, Harold, 1907
  Children's Aid Society (New York, N.Y.), 1906
  Childs, Albert H., 1913
  Childs, Asa P., Jr., 1886-1916
  Childs, Caroline D., Oct 19 [no year]
  Childs, Clinton L., 1918
  Childs, Harvey, Jr., 1893-1915
- Childs, Howard - Childs Marshall (Box 22, Folder 3)
  Childs, Howard, 1907
  Childs, James A., 1920
  Childs, James Asa, 1900, 1916
  Childs, James H., 1913
  Childs, Jennie P. [Mrs. Charles A. Childs], 1919-1922
  Childs, Lilly Rankin, 1899-1919
  Childs, Lowrie, 1896-1897
  Childs, Lyman B., 1909-1913
  Childs, Marshall, 1889-1902
- Childs, Martha - Chisholm (Box 22, Folder 4)
  Childs, Martha H., [1890's], 1900-1911
  Childs, Starling W., 1916
  Childs, W. St. Clair, 1919
  Childs, Wallace, 1900
  Chipley, C.A., 1886-1889
  Chisholm, Stewart H., 1893-1898, 1910
- Choate - Church of the Ascension (Box 22, Folder 5)
  Choate, Joseph H., 1913-1914
  Choctaw, Oklahoma and Gulf Railroad Co. (Cincinnati, Ohio), 1902
  Christian Home for Working Girls [Pittsburgh, Pa.], 1901-1902
  Christian Science Publishing Society (Boston, Mass.), 1919
  Christmas Seal Committee (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1923
  Christy, Walter J., 1911
  Chrystie, T. Ludlow, 1906
  Chubb, A.L., 1917
  Chubb, C.F., 1917-1922
  Church Club of the Diocese of Pittsburgh (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1919
  Church of the Ascension (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1900
- Church, S.H. - City Contracting (Box 22, Folder 6)
  Church, S.H., [dates?]
  Church, W.C. and F.P., 1894
  Churchill, Henry C., 1916
  Cichocki, Henry, 1899
  Citizens Committee for Perpetuating the Dewey Arch (New York, N.Y.) - See: T.B. Dean
  Citizens Insurance Co. (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1885-1886
  Citizens National Bank (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1902
  City and Suburban Homes Co. [no place], 1910
  City Contracting Co. (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1915
- City Deposit Bank (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1887-1918 (Box 22, Folder 7-8)
- City Midday - Claire (Box 22, Folder 9)
  City Midday Club (New York, N.Y.), 1901-1921
  City Trust, Safe Deposit and Surety Co. of Philadelphia (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1903
  Civic Club of Allegheny County [Pittsburgh, Pa.], 1913
  Civic Forum (New York, N.Y.), 1910-1913
  Civil Service Reform Association (New York, N.Y.), 1914-1915
  Claflin, John, 1910
  Clagett, W.H., [1906]
  Claire, John, Mrs., [1907]
- Clairton - Clark, Earl (Box 22, Folder 10)
  Clairton Street Railway Co. (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1905-1911
  Clapp, Charles E., 1901-1919
  Clapp, Charles E., Jr., 1923
  Clapp, D.C., 1893
  Clapp, Delia D. [Mrs. D.C. Clapp], 1901-1902
  Clapp, Harold C., 1915
  Clark and Cray (Dunbar, Pa.) - See: J.R. Cray
  Clark, Charles, 1903
  Clark, Charles J., 1901
  Clark, Chas W., 1896
  Clark, Earl S., 1907
- Clark, Edward - Clarke (Box 22, Folder 11)
  Clark, Edward H., 1908, 1913
  Clark, Edwin H., 1904
  Clark, F.J., 1917
  Clark, F.L., 1896
  Clark, Frank B., 1903
  Clark, Geo. W., 1898
  Clark, George Lemist, 1912
  Clark, James, 1894
  Clark, Marian K., 1918
  Clark, Marshall, 1903
  Clark, Noble M., 1897
  Clark, W.A., Mrs., 1915
  Clark, William A., 1916
  Clarke, A.E. Stanley, 1916
  Clarke, C.C., 1893
  Clarke, Dumont, 1898
  Clarke, E.A.S., 1912
  Clarke, John D., 1909
  Clarke, Lewis L., 1918-1919
- Clarkin - Cleveland (Box 23, Folder 1)
  Clarkin, Franklin, 1912
  Clay, Geo. W., 1898
  Clay, Lucius, 1914
  Clay, W.F., 1914
  Clayton, Edward, 1917
  Cleal, Joseph P., 1919
  Cleaner, Harold V., 1900
  Cleland, J.W., 1900
  Clemson, D.M., 1891
  Cleveland, Grover, 1893
  Cleveland Hardware Co. (Cleveland, Ohio), 1900
  Cleveland, J. Wray, 1906-1907
  Cleveland Museum of Art (Cleveland, Ohio), 1916-1918
  Cleveland School of Art [Cleveland, Ohio], 1910
- Clifford - Coal (Box 23, Folder 2)
  Clifford and Lawton (New York, N.Y.), 1914
  Clingerman, Walter H., 1915-1919
  Clinkaberry, Henry T., 1897
  Clinton Iron and Steel Co. (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1896
  Cloutier, Sam, 1913
  Clow, James B., 1899
  Clow, W.S., 1897-1901
  Cluley, John F., 1887
  Coal Trade Journal(New York, N.Y.), 1905-1917
- Cobb - Coffin (Box 23, Folder 3)
  Cobb, Frank J., 1918
  Coble, D.H., 1913
  Cochran, Isaac, 1890
  Cochran, R.H., 1887
  Cochrane, Mary [L.?], 1912
  Cochrane, L.M., Mrs., 1893
  Cockings, Thomas G., 1891
  Codman, John S., 1914
  Codman, Ogden, 1907
  Coe, W.W., 1906
  Coffin and Co. (New York, N.Y.), 1908, 1915
  Coffin, C.P., 1893, 1896
  Coffin, Charles A., 1904-1918
  Coffin, F.A., 1902
  Coffin, Lemuel, 1886
  Coffin, William A., 1898, 1901
- Coffman - Coles (Box 23, Folder 4)
  Coffman, W.H., 1899
  Coffrain, Lewis D., 1903
  Cogswell, Wilbur F., 1905
  Cohen, Carrie N. [Mrs. Josiah Cohen], 1901
  Cohill, Clara Curtis [Mrs. Geo. H. Cohill], 1896
  Coke Company of Connellsville (Baltimore, Md.), 1889
  Col. J.W. Patterson Corps, No. 1 (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1916
  Colburn, R.T., 1907
  Colby, Francis, [ca. 1914-1918]
  Cole, B.D., 1906
  Cole, Charles L., 1909
  Cole, E.E., 1906
  Cole, Frank T., 1907
  Cole, Leland H., 1916
  Cole, T.F., 1907
  Coleman and Brock (Lebanon, Pa.), 1891
  Coleman, J. Howard, 1914
  Coleman, John C., 1909-1910
  Coleman, W.H., 1901
  Coles, J. Ackerman, 1911
- Colgate - Colonial (Box 23, Folder 5)
  Colgate Hoyt and Co. (New York, N.Y.), 1906
  College for Women [Pittsburgh, Pa.?], 1914
  College of Jersey City (Jersey City, N.J.), 1915
  College of St. Francis Xavier [no place], 1916
  College of the City of New York (New York, N.Y.), 1912
  Collier, J.H., 1914
  Collier, Wm. Miller, [1910]
  Collier Engineer(Scranton, Pa.), 1891
  Collier Engineer Co. (Scranton, Pa.), 1896
  Collins, Amelia, 1898
  Collins, F.W., 1909
  Collins, H.E., 1890-1892, 1911
  Collins, S., 1915
  Colman, Norman J., 1887
  Colonial Club of Princeton University (Princeton, N.J.), 1908
  Colonial Steel Co. (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1909-1915
  Colonial Trust Co. (New York, N.Y.), 1906
- Colonnade - Columbia (Box 23, Folder 6)
  Colonnade Co. (Cleveland, Ohio), 1918, 1921
  Colorado Light and Power Co. (Canon City, Col.), 1909
  Colt, H.S., 1908
  Colton, Henry E., 1913
  Columbia Bank (New York, N.Y.), 1914
  Columbia Chemical Co. (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1899-1920
  Columbia University (New York, N.Y.), 1908-1916
- Columbian - Committee (Box 23, Folder 7)
  Columbian Bronze Corp. (New York, N.Y.), 1919
  Columbian Engraving and Publishing Co. (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1893
  Columbus, Hocking Valley and Toledo Railway Co. (Columbus, Ohio), 1888
  Columbus Iron and Steel Co. (Columbus, Ohio), 1903
  Colvin, J.T., 1893
  Colwell Granite Co. (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1919
  Combined News Service, Inc. (New York, N.Y.), 1910
  Commercial and Financial Chronicle(New York, N.Y.), 1899
  Commercial Club of Indiana Harbor and East Chicago (Indiana Harbor, Ind.), 1909
  Commercial National Bank (Chicago, Ill.), 1899-1900
  Commercial Trust Co. (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1902-1911
  Commercial Union Insurance Co., Ltd. (New York, N.Y.), 1920
  Committee of Chauffeurs [no place], 1918
- Commonwealth Real Estate and Trust Co. (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1902 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Commonwealth Real Estate Co. (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1903-1913 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Commonwealth Trust - Connellsville Coke (Box 23, Folder 10)
  Commonwealth Trust Co. (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1916
  Communipau Coal Co. (New York, N.Y.), 1900
  Compton, Chas. R., 1912
  Compton, T.W., 1916
  Congdon, Chester A., 1909
  Conger, A.L., 1897
  Conghenour, B.T., Mrs., 1890
  Congressional Country Club (Washington, D.C.), 1922
  Congreve, J.G., 1914-1916
  Conn, C.A., 1902
  Conn. Mutual Life Insurance Co. (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1904
  Connellsville, Pa. - Centennial, 1906
  Connellsville, Pa. - Homecoming celebration for soldiers, sailors, and marines, 1919
  Connellsville, Pa. - Park, 1909
  Connellsville, Pa. - Trinity Lutheran Church, 1909-1911
  Connellsville Coke and Iron Co. (Mauch Chunk, Pa., and Philadelphia, Pa.), 1885-1889
- Connellsville Gas - Connelly (Box 23, Folder 11)
  Connellsville Gas Coal Co. (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1886-1895
  Connellsville Masonic Association (Connellsville, Pa.), 1909
  Connelly, Eugene L., 1905
  Connelly, W.C., Jr., 1896, 1898
  Connelly, W.C., Jr., Mrs., 1912
- Conner - Converse (Box 24, Folder 1)
  Conner, Chas. D., 1887, 1892
  Conner, H.P., 1905, 1907
  Connfelt, Una Soley, 1916
  Connolly Brothers (Beverly Farms, Mass.), 1907
  Connolly, Gregory P., 1905, 1907
  Connolly, John, 1900
  Connor, Albert, 1917
  Connor, Washington, 1894
  Conrad, G.W., 1903
  Conried Metropolitan Opera Company (New York, N.Y.), 1906
  Conrow, Wilford S., 1916
  Consolidated Gas Co. of New York (New York, N.Y.), 1914-1919
  Consolidation Coal Co. [no place], 1916
  Constans, J.J., 1898
  Content, Ada [Mrs. Harry Content], 1912
  Conti, Cesare, 1909
  Continental Guaranty Corp. (New York, N.Y.), 1919
  Convent of Mercy (Cresson, Pa.), 1898
  Convent of Mercy [Pittsburgh, Pa.], 1896
  Convent of the Good Shepherd (Allegheny City, Pa.), 1886
  Converse, E.C., 1891, 1911
  Converse, H.P., 1897
- Cook - Coolidge (Box 24, Folder 2)
  Cook, Chas., 1907
  Cook, George E.[?], 1911
  Cook, William H., 1906
  Cooke, Jay, III, 1901-1919
  Cooke, R.B., 1916
  Cooke, Robert Grier, 1906-1909
  Cookson, John W., 1903
  Coolbaugh, F.W., 1899
  Coolidge, Harold Jefferson, 1906, 1916
  Coolidge, H.J., Mrs., 1908
  Coolidge, T. Jefferson, Jr., 1903-1907
- Cooper - Corcoran (Box 24, Folder 3)
  Cooper, Harry, 1915
  Cooper, Isabel S., 1912
  Cooper, J.G., 1915
  Cope, Pierson, 1889
  Copeland, E.L., 1912
  Copeland, Guild A., 1904
  Copley Society of Boston (Boston, Mass.), 1904, 1911
  Corbett, W.H., 1893-1900
  Corbin, W. Terence[?], 1903
  Corkum, Alex C., 1909
  Corcoran, W.D., 1891-1894
- Core - Corley (Box 24, Folder 4)
  Core and Herbert [no place], 1912
  Corey, J.B., 1891
  Corry, William E., 1894-1911
  Corkum, Alexander C., 1909
  Corless, M.N.K., 1912
  Corley, Ames H., 1915
  Corley, Henriette H. [Mrs. Ames H. Corley], 1915
- Corn - Cotting (Box 24, Folder 5)
  Corn Exchange Bank (New York, N.Y.), 1912
  Cornelius, Richard, 1893, 1896
  Corning, Nicodemus J., 1895
  Corona Typewriter Co., Inc. (New York, N.Y.), 1918
  Corporation Debenture Co. (New York, N.Y.), 1903
  Corporation Trust Company of New Jersey (Jersey City, N.J.), 1899
  Cortelyou, George B., 1898-1906
  Corwine, William R., 1906
  Cosgrave Brothers (New York, N.Y.), 1905
  Cosmopolitan Magazine(Irvington-on-Hudson, N.Y.), 1902-1903
  Cossey, Robert, 1920
  Coster, M.E. [Doe Ye Nexte Thynge Society], 1914
  Cotter, Arundel, 1915
  Cottier and Co. (New York, N.Y.), 1904-1909
  Cotting, Francis J., 1906
- Couch - Coyne (Box 24, Folder 6)
  Couch, Lester S., 1918
  Couch, Louis Bradford, 1912
  Coulby, H., 1908
  Coulter, A.C., 1905
  Country Club (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1902-1910
  Country Club of Augusta (Augusta, Ga.), 1910
  County, A.J., 1918
  Courier(Connellsville, Pa.), 1891, 1905, 1919
  Courtland Babcock and Co. (New York, N.Y.), 1899
  Courtney, Gladys V., 1917
  Cowan, Frank, 1895
  Cowan, Ja[me]s A., 1898, 1902
  Cowan, James B.O., 1905
  Cowell, Arthur Westcott, 1920
  Cowley, John, 1898
  Cox and Stevens (New York, N.Y.), 1911
  Cox, John F., 1893, 1900
  Coyan, Sadie, 1907
  Coykendall, L.T., 1908
  Coyle Brothers, 1908, 1917
  Coyne, Mary, undated
- Crabbe - Cranston (Box 24, Folder 7)
  Crabbe, W.R., 1900-1901
  Cracraft, C.C., 1895
  Craig, E., 1902
  Craig, Edwin S., 1898
  Craig, Emma M., 1901
  Craig, Jacob, Jr., 1889
  Craig, P.L., 1903
  Craig, R.H., 1915
  Craigee, Montrose, 1915
  Craigie, A. Walpole, 1916
  Craley, Edmund P., 1903-1904
  Cramer, John H., 1902
  Cramer, L.W., 1916
  Cramp, Charles H., 1899, 1902, undated
  Cramp, Edwin S., 1896, 1899
  Cranston, Edith, 1912-1913
- Craufurd - Cree (Box 24, Folder 8)
  Craufurd, James L., 1913
  Cravath, Henderson and de Gersdorff [no place], 1909
  Cravath, Paul D., 1914
  Crawford, Everett L., 1915
  Cray, J.R., 1889
  Cray, James R., 1917
  Cree, J.W., Jr., 1919
  Cree, Thomas K., 1900